Guide to the International Brotherhood of Teamsters Newspapers and Journals collection 1956-2002 IBT0031
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
IBT Newspapers and Journals collection
1904-2011
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen, and Helpers of America
International Brotherhood of Teamsters
IBT0031
12.5 Linear Feet
This collection contains newspapers and newsletters published by IBT locals, joint councils and other Teamsters organizations from 1904-2009. The bulk of the materials are IBT local and joint council periodicals from a number of different cities, including New York, Chicago, Washington, D.C., Los Angeles, Pittsburgh, Cleveland, Denver, Milwaukee, Seattle and Vancouver, B.C.
Conditions Governing Access
This collection is open for research.
Arrangement
The collection is arranged alphabetically and chronologically.
Scope and Contents
This collection contains newspapers and newsletters published by IBT locals, joint councils and other Teamsters organizations from 1904-2009. The bulk of the materials are IBT local and joint council periodicals from a number of different cities, including New York, Chicago, Washington, D.C., Los Angeles, Pittsburgh, Cleveland, Denver, Milwaukee, Seattle and Vancouver, B.C. The papers cover general union and labor news, IBT-related news and events, as well as current political news, events and commentary. As most of the materials date from 1957-1990, they document the entire Jimmy Hoffa era, as well as the tenures of Frank Fitzsimmons, Roy Williams, Jackie Presser, and William McCarthy. Also included in the collection are the DRIVE Reporter, the publication of the Teamsters' Democratic, Republican and the Independent Voter Education organization.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Transferred by the International Brotherhood of Teamsters, 2012 [2012.036]
Biographical / Historical
This collection contains newspapers and newsletters published by IBT locals, joint councils and other Teamsters organizations from 1956-2002. These newspapers span a wide range of Teamster history and show how each era affected different regions and sections of IBT.
Newspapers; Labor unions -- United States -- History -- 20th century; Labor unions; Labor and laboring classes
- American Products Exclusively for Teamsters Families from Directly Yours, Inc., 1984; Series 1 (Box 30, Folder 6)
- B.C. Teamster, 1967-1968 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  General
  Published by IBT Joint Council 36, Vancouver, B.C., Canada.
- British Columbia / Yukon Teamster, 1981 November - 1986 December (Box 1, Folder 2)
- DRIVE Reporter, 1960-1963 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- DRIVE Reporter, 1963 December 15 - 1965 February 15 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  Publication of the IBT Democratic, Republican, Independent Voter Education organization.
- Focus: Official Weekly Publication by the International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Vol. 2, No. 1, January 1, 1973; Series 1 (Box 30, Folder 4)
- HRC News: The Teamster Human Rights Commission Newsletter, March 2010; Series 1 (Box 30, Folder 10)
- International Teamsters Retiree News, 1983-1991 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Joint Council 13 Research Bulletin, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Joint Council 40 News, 1973-1983 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  Publication of IBT Joint Council 40, Pittsburgh, PA.
- Joint Council 41-'Teamster', 1994 (Box 26, Folder 3)
- Joint Council 69 News, 1977-1982 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  Publication of IBT Joint Council 69, Indianapolis, IN.
- Joint Council 92-The Member's Bulletin, Vol. 2-6, 1995-1997 (Box 26, Folder 5)
- Local 20 - "Team and Wheel", 1959 December 31 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  Publication of IBT Local 20, Toledo, OH.
- Local 25-"The Spokesman", Winter, 2011 (Box 26, Folder 14)
- Local 63 News Watch, Vol 3-12', 1995-2000 (Box 26, Folder 6)
- Local 82 News, Vol. 2, No. 1, January - March 2008; Series 1 (Box 30, Folder 8)
- Local 120 'Power Press'-Vol 1, No.1, 2004 (Box 26, Folder 10)
- Local 122 Perspectives, Vol. 1, No. 2, Summer 2008; Series 1 (Box 30, Folder 9)
- Local 190, 2003-2009 (Box 26, Folder 9)
- Local 237 Newsletter, 1998 December - 1999 February (Box 1, Folder 8)
  Publication of IBT Local 237, New York, NY.
- Local 243 - "Mirror Mirror", 1999 January - February (Box 1, Folder 9)
  Publication of IBT Local 243, Detroit, MI.
- Local 299 News, 1970-1973 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  Publication of IBT Local 299, Monroe, MI.
- Local 315-Vol. 16, 2009 (Box 26, Folder 12)
- Local 337 News, 1970-1973 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  Publication of IBT Local 337, Detroit, MI.
- Local 391-"The Voice of Teamsters 391" Vol 34, January, 1999 (Box 26, Folder 8)
- Local 507 News Mailer re: Blood Drives, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  Publication of IBT Local 507, Cleveland, OH.
- Local 507 News Mailer re: Christmas Parties, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Local 507 News Mailer re: Contract Settlements, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Local 507 News Mailer re: Easter Seal Telethon, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Local 507 News Mailer re: Health and Welfare Benefits, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Local 507 News Mailer - Miscellaneous, 1985-1986 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Local 507 News Mailer re: Pension Fund, 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Local 507 News Mailer re: Sports, 1984-1986 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Local 507 News Mailer - Summary Financial Reports, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Local 507 News Mailer re: Truck Roadeos, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Local 572 'Reporter-Vol. 11-13', 1995-1997 (Box 26, Folder 4)
- Local 743 Bulletin, 1973-1974 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  Publication of IBT Local 743, Chicago, IL.
- Local 473-"Voice of 743" Vol. 13-24 & "Portrait of a Union" booklet, Ocotber 1970-November, 1981 (Box 26, Folder 1)
- Local 747-"Flight Deck Quarterly"-Issue 3, 2004 (Box 26, Folder 11)
- Local 814 News, 1970 June (Box 2, Folder 8)
  Publication of IBT Local 814, New York, NY.
- Local 952-"Reporter Vol. 6-7", 1995-2000 (Box 26, Folder 7)
- Local 986 Reporter, 1984 (Box 26, Folder 2)
- Maryland Teamster, 1970-1981 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  Publication of IBT Joint Council 62, Washington, DC.
- Michigan Conference of Teamsters Welfare Fund-Messenger-Vol. 27, 2009 (Box 26, Folder 13)
- Minnesota Teamster, 1983-1985 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  Publication of IBT Joint Council 32, Minneapolis, MN.
- Missouri Teamster, 1969 June 20 - 1970 June 19 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  Publication of IBT Joint Council 13, St. Louis, MO.
- Missouri Teamster, Vol. 16, No. 6, June 2011; Series 1 (Box 30, Folder 12)
- Montgomery Ward Union News, 1958 May - 1959 July (Box 2, Folder 12)
  Pubished by the Teamsters Montgomery Ward Council.
- Northern California Teamster, 1968 September - 1971 August (Box 2, Folder 13)
  Publication of IBT Joint Council 7, San Francisco, CA.
- The Ohio Teamster, 1976-1978 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  Publication of IBT Ohio Joint Councils, Cleveland, OH.
- The Ohio Teamster, 1979-1980 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- The Ohio Teamster, 1982-1983 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- The Ohio Teamster, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- The Ohio Teamster, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- The Ohio Teamster, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Oregon Teamster, 1982-1984 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  Publication of IBT Joint Council 37, Portland, OR.
- Report from Washington, November 1968 - May 1970; Series 1 (Box 30, Folder 3)
- Rocky Mountain Teamster, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  Publication of IBT Joint Council 3, Denver, CO.
- Rocky Mountain Teamster, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Rocky Mountain Teamster, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Rocky Mountain Teamster, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Rocky Mountain Teamster, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Southern California Teamster, 1956-1958 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  Publication of IBT Joint Council 42, Los Angeles, CA.
- Southern California Teamster, 1960 December 7 - 1961 October 31 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Southern California Teamster, 1963 January 9 - August 21 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Southern California Teamster, 1963 August 28 - 1964 February 26 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Southern California Teamster, 1964 March 4 - July 1 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Southern California Teamster, 1964 July 8 - October 7 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Southern California Teamster, 1964 October 14 - December 2 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Southern California Teamster, 1964 December 9 - 1965 March 3 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Southern California Teamster, 1965 March 10 - June 9 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Southern California Teamster, 1965 June 9 - September 1 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Southern California Teamster, 1965 September 8 - November 10 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Southern California Teamster, 1965 November 17 - 1966 January 26 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Southern California Teamster, 1966 February 2 - June 1 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Southern California Teamster, 1966 June 8 - October 5 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Southern California Teamster, 1966 October 12 - 1967 January 11 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Southern California Teamster, 1967 January 18 - March 22 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Southern California Teamster, 1967 March 29 - June 7 (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Southern California Teamster, 1967 June 14 - September 6 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Southern California Teamster, 1967 September 13 - December 6 (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Southern California Teamster, 1967 December 13 - 1968 March 6 (Box 7, Folder 3)
- Southern California Teamster, 1968 March 13 - July 10 (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Southern California Teamster, 1968 July 17 - September 25 (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Southern California Teamster, 1968 October 2 - 1969 February 12 (Box 7, Folder 6)
- Southern California Teamster, 1969 February 19 - May 21 (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Southern California Teamster, 1969 May 28 - September 3 (Box 8, Folder 2)
- Southern California Teamster, 1969 September 10 - December 24 (Box 8, Folder 3)
- Southern California Teamster, 1970 January 14 - May 6 (Box 8, Folder 4)
- Southern California Teamster, 1970 May 13 - July 29 (Box 8, Folder 5)
- Southern California Teamster, 1970 August 5 - November 11 (Box 8, Folder 6)
- Southern California Teamster, 1970 November 18 - 1971 March 3 (Box 9, Folder 1)
- Southern California Teamster, 1971 March 10 - July 28 (Box 9, Folder 2)
- Southern California Teamster, 1971 August 4 - December 22 (Box 9, Folder 3)
- Southern California Teamster, 1972 January 12 - 1973 June 6 (Box 9, Folder 4)
- Southern California Teamster, 1973 June 13 - October 17 (Box 9, Folder 5)
- Southern California Teamster, 1973 October 24 - 1974 March 13 (Box 9, Folder 6)
- Southern California Teamster, 1974 March 10 - July 10 (Box 10, Folder 1)
- Southern California Teamster, 1974 July 24 - 1975 March 5 (Box 10, Folder 2)
- Southern California Teamster, 1975 March 19 - 1977 September 21 (Box 10, Folder 3)
- Southern California Teamster, 1978 January 11 - October 4 (Box 10, Folder 4)
- Southern California Teamster, 1978 October 18 - 1979 June 20 (Box 10, Folder 5)
- Southern California Teamster, 1979 July 5 - 1980 March 20 (Box 10, Folder 6)
- Southern California Teamster, 1980 March 26 - December 10 (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Southern California Teamster, 1981 January 14 - September 16 (Box 11, Folder 2)
- Southern California Teamster, 1981 September 30 - 1982 June 23 (Box 11, Folder 3)
- Southern California Teamster, 1982 July 21 - 1983 February 16 (Box 11, Folder 4)
- Southern California Teamster, 1983 March 23 - December 14 (Box 11, Folder 5)
- Southern California Teamster, 1984 January 14 - May 22 (Box 11, Folder 6)
- Southern California Teamster, 1985 June 19 - 1986 October 22 (Box 12, Folder 1)
- Southern California Teamster, 1986 November 19 - 1988 March 23 (Box 12, Folder 2)
- Southern California Teamster, 1988 April 20 - 1990 September 19 (Box 12, Folder 3)
- Southern California Teamster, 1990 October 24 - 2002 September 18 (Box 12, Folder 4)
- The Teamster News, 1984-1986 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  Publication of IBT Local 863, Mountainside, NJ.
- Teamsters News Release, 18-month Strike Settlement, 1987; Series 1 (Box 30, Folder 7)
- Teamster Retiree News, January - February 2011; Series 1 (Box 30, Folder 11)
- Texas Conference of Teamsters, 1983-1984 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  Publication of the Texas Conference of Teamsters.
- Upstate Teamster, 1980 December - 1981 July (Box 12, Folder 7)
  Publication of IBT Joint Council 18, Utica, NY.
- Upstate Teamster, 1981 August - 1982 January (Box 13, Folder 1)
- Upstate Teamster, 1982 April - October (Box 13, Folder 2)
- Upstate Teamster, 1982 November - 1983 February (Box 13, Folder 3)
- Upstate Teamster, 1983 March - May (Box 13, Folder 4)
- Upstate Teamster, 1983 June - August (Box 13, Folder 5)
- Upstate Teamster, 1983 September - October (Box 13, Folder 6)
- Upstate Teamster, 1983 November - December (Box 14, Folder 1)
- Upstate Teamster, 1984 January - February (Box 14, Folder 2)
- Upstate Teamster, 1984 March - April (Box 14, Folder 3)
- Upstate Teamster, 1984 May - 1985 January (Box 14, Folder 4)
- Upstate Teamster, 1985 February - June (Box 14, Folder 5)
- Upstate Teamster, 1985 July - October (Box 14, Folder 6)
- Upstate Teamsters, 1986 January - March (Box 15, Folder 1)
- Upstate Teamsters, 1986 April - July (Box 15, Folder 2)
- Washington Teamster, 1939-1942 (Oversize 22, Folder 1)
- Washington Teamster, 1943 (Oversize 22, Folder 2)
- Washington Teamster, 1944 (Oversize 23, Folder 1)
- Washington Teamster, 1945 (Oversize 23, Folder 2)
- Washington Teamster, 1946 (Oversize 24, Folder 1)
- Washington Teamster, 1947 (Oversize 24, Folder 2)
- Washington Teamster, 1948 (Oversize 25, Folder 1)
- Washington Teamster, 1949 (Oversize 25, Folder 2)
- Washington Teamster, 1982 January 8 - April 30 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  Publication of IBT Joint Council 28, Seattle, WA.
- Washington Teamster, 1982 May 7 - October 1 (Box 15, Folder 4)
- Washington Teamster, 1982 December 1 - 1983 May 1 (Box 15, Folder 5)
- Washington Teamster, 1983 June 1 - 1984 January 1 (Box 15, Folder 6)
- Washington Teamster, 1984 February 1 - August 1 (Box 16, Folder 1)
- Washington Teamster, 1984 September 1 - 1985 May 1 (Box 16, Folder 2)
- Washington Teamster, 1985 June 1 - October 1 (Box 16, Folder 3)
- Washington Teamster, 1985 November 1 - 1986 July 1 (Box 16, Folder 4)
- Washington Teamster, 1986 August 1 - 1987 January 1 (Box 16, Folder 5)
- Washington Teamster, 1987 February 1 - 1988 April (Box 16, Folder 6)
- Washington Teamster, 1988 July - October (Box 16, Folder 7)
- Wisconsin Teamster, 1968 September (Box 16, Folder 8)
  Publication of IBT Joint Council 39, Milwaukee, WI.
- Wisconsin Teamster, 1979 May - 1982 July (Box 17, Folder 1)
- Wisconsin Teamster, 1982 August - 1983 October (Box 17, Folder 2)
- Wisconsin Teamster, 1984 January - December (Box 17, Folder 3)
- Wisconsin Teamster, 1985 January - November (Box 17, Folder 4)
- Wisconsin Teamster, 1986 January - December (Box 17, Folder 5)
- Wisconsin Teamster, 1987 January - October (Box 17, Folder 6)
- Wisconsin Teamster, 1988 January - December (Box 17, Folder 7)
- Voice of 743, November 1957 - December 1958 (Oversize 18, Folder 1)
- Voice of 743, November 1957 - December 1958 (Oversize 18, Folder 2)
- Voice of 743, 1959 (Oversize 18, Folder 3)
- Voice of 743, 1959 (Oversize 18, Folder 4)
- Voice of 743, 1959 (Oversize 18, Folder 5)
- Voice of 743, 1960 (Oversize 18, Folder 6)
- Voice of 743, 1961 (Oversize 18, Folder 7)
- Voice of 743, 1961-1962 (Oversize 18, Folder 8)
- Voice of 743, 1962 (Oversize 18, Folder 9)
- Voice of 743, 1963 (Oversize 19, Folder 1)
- Voice of 743, 1963-1964 (Oversize 19, Folder 2)
- Voice of 743, 1964-1965 (Oversize 19, Folder 3)
- Voice of 743, 1965 (Oversize 19, Folder 4)
- Voice of 743, 1966 (Oversize 19, Folder 5)
- Voice of 743, 1966-1968 (Oversize 19, Folder 6)
- Voice of 743, 1967 (Oversize 19, Folder 7)
- Voice of 743, 1968 (Oversize 19, Folder 8)
- Voice of 743, 1969 (Oversize 20, Folder 1)
- Voice of 743, 1969-1970 (Oversize 20, Folder 2)
- Voice of 743, 1970 (Oversize 20, Folder 3)
- Voice of 743, 1971 (Oversize 20, Folder 4)
- Voice of 743, 1972 (Oversize 20, Folder 5)
- Voice of 743, 1973 (Oversize 20, Folder 6)
- Voice of 743, 1974 (Oversize 20, Folder 7)
- Voice of 743, 1975 (Oversize 20, Folder 8)
- Voice of 743, 1976-1980 (Oversize 20, Folder 9)
- Voice of 743, 1982-1985 (Oversize 20, Folder 10)
- Voice of 743, 1986-1989 (Oversize 20, Folder 11)
- Joint Council No.42, November 11, 1981 (Box 21, Folder 1)
- Joint Council No.42 Southern California Teamster, November 30, 1983 (Box 21, Folder 2)
- Joint Council No. 42 Southern California Teamster, January 18, 1984 (Box 21, Folder 3)
- Joint Council No. 42 Southern California Teamster, February 15, 1984 (Box 21, Folder 4)
- Joint Council No. 42 Southern California Teamster, March 14, 1984 (Box 21, Folder 5)
- Joint Council No. 42 Southern California Teamster, April 18, 1984 (Box 21, Folder 6)
- Joint Council No. 42 Southern California Teamster, September 14, 1983 (Box 21, Folder 7)
- Joint Council No. 42 Southern California Teamster, November 9, 1983 (Box 21, Folder 8)
- Joint Council No. 42 Southern California Teamster, June 15, 1983 (Box 21, Folder 9)
- Joint Council No. 42 Southern California Teamster, May 18, 1983 (Box 21, Folder 10)
- Joint Council No. 42 Southern California Teamster, April 20, 1983 (Box 21, Folder 11)
- Joint Council No. 42 Southern California Teamster, February 16, 1983 (Box 21, Folder 12)
- Joint Council No. 42 Southern California Teamster, January 19, 1983 (Box 21, Folder 13)
- Joint Council No. 42 Southern California Teamster, December 15, 1982 (Box 21, Folder 14)
- Joint Council No. 42 Southern California Teamster, November 24, 1982 (Box 21, Folder 15)
- Joint Council No. 42 Southern California Teamster, November 10, 1982 (Box 21, Folder 16)
- Joint Council No. 42 Southern California Teamster, October 27, 1982 (Box 21, Folder 17)
- Joint Council No. 42 Southern California Teamster, September 22, 1982 (Box 21, Folder 18)
- Joint Council No. 42 Southern California Teamster, February 24, 1982 (Box 21, Folder 19)
- Joint Council No. 42 Southern California Teamster, November 25, 1981 (Box 21, Folder 20)
- Joint Council No. 42 Southern California Teamster, June 10, 1981 (Box 21, Folder 21)
- Joint Council No. 42 Southern California Teamster, September 17, 1986 (Box 21, Folder 22)
- Joint Council No. 42 Southern California Teamster, October 22, 1986 (Box 21, Folder 23)
- Joint Council No. 42 Southern California Teamster, November 19, 1986 (Box 21, Folder 24)
- Joint Council No. 42 Southern California Teamster, February 11, 1987 (Box 21, Folder 25)
- Joint Council No. 42 Southern California Teamster, March 11, 1987 (Box 21, Folder 26)
- Joint Council No. 42 Southern California Teamster, April 8, 1987 (Box 21, Folder 27)
- Joint Council No. 42 Southern California Teamster, May 13, 1987 (Box 21, Folder 28)
- Joint Council No. 42 Southern California Teamster, June 17, 1987 (Box 21, Folder 29)
- Joint Council No. 42 Southern California Teamster, July 22, 1987 (Box 21, Folder 30)
- Joint Council No. 42 Southern California Teamster, August 19, 1987 (Box 21, Folder 31)
- Joint Council No. 42 Southern California Teamster, September 11, 1985 (Box 21, Folder 32)
- Joint Council No. 42 Southern California Teamster, October 9, 1985 (Box 21, Folder 33)
- Joint Council No. 42 Southern California Teamster, November 6, 1985 (Box 21, Folder 34)
- Joint Council No. 42 Southern California Teamster, December 11, 1985 (Box 21, Folder 35)
- Joint Council No. 42 Southern California Teamster, January 15, 1986 (Box 21, Folder 36)
- Joint Council No. 42 Southern California Teamster, February 12, 1986 (Box 21, Folder 37)
- Joint Council No. 42 Southern California Teamster, March 19, 1986 (Box 21, Folder 38)
- Joint Council No. 42 Southern California Teamster, April 16, 1986 (Box 21, Folder 39)
- Joint Council No. 42 Southern California Teamster, May 14, 1986 (Box 21, Folder 40)
- Joint Council No. 42 Southern California Teamster, July 23, 1986 (Box 21, Folder 41)
- Joint Council No. 42 Southern California Teamster, May 16, 1984 (Box 21, Folder 42)
- Joint Council No. 42 Southern California Teamster, July 25, 1984 (Box 21, Folder 43)
- Joint Council No. 42 Southern California Teamster, August 22, 1984 (Box 21, Folder 44)
- Joint Council No. 42 Southern California Teamster, September 19, 1984 (Box 21, Folder 45)
- Joint Council No. 42 Southern California Teamster, October 24, 1984 (Box 21, Folder 46)
- Joint Council No. 42 Southern California Teamster, November 21, 1984 (Box 21, Folder 47)
- Joint Council No. 42 Southern California Teamster, January 23, 1985 (Box 21, Folder 48)
- Joint Council No. 42 Southern California Teamster, March 20, 1985 (Box 21, Folder 49)
- Joint Council No. 42 Southern California Teamster, April 24, 1985 (Box 21, Folder 50)
- Joint Council No. 42 Southern California Teamster, May 22, 1985 (Box 21, Folder 51)
- Joint Council No. 42 Southern California Teamster, June 19, 1985 (Box 21, Folder 52)
- Joint Council No. 42 Southern California Teamster, July 17, 1985 (Box 21, Folder 53)
- Joint Council No. 42 Southern California Teamster, September 16, 1987 (Box 21, Folder 54)
- Joint Council No. 42 Southern California Teamster, October 14, 1987 (Box 21, Folder 55)
- Joint Council No. 42 Southern California Teamster, July 20, 1988 (Box 21, Folder 56)
- Joint Council No. 42 Southern California Teamster, August 17, 1988 (Box 21, Folder 57)
- Joint Council No. 42 Southern California Teamster, September 14, 1988 (Box 21, Folder 58)
- Joint Council No. 42 Southern California Teamster, October 19, 1988 (Box 21, Folder 59)
- Joint Council No. 42 Southern California Teamster, November 16, 1988 (Box 21, Folder 60)
- Joint Council No. 42 Southern California Teamster, December 14, 1988 (Box 21, Folder 61)
- Joint Council No. 42 Southern California Teamster, January 11, 1989 (Box 21, Folder 62)
- Joint Council No. 42 Southern California Teamster, February 8, 1989 (Box 21, Folder 63)
- Joint Council No. 42 Southern California Teamster, March 8, 1989 (Box 21, Folder 64)
- Joint Council No. 42 Southern California Teamster, April 5, 1989 (Box 21, Folder 65)
- Joint Council No. 42 Southern California Teamster, May 10, 1989 (Box 21, Folder 66)
- Joint Council No. 42 Southern California Teamster, June 7, 1989 (Box 21, Folder 67)
- Joint Council No. 42 Southern California Teamster, July 15, 1989 (Box 21, Folder 68)
- Joint Council No. 42 Southern California Teamster, August 2, 1989 (Box 21, Folder 69)
- Joint Council No. 42 Southern California Teamster, September 6, 1989 (Box 21, Folder 70)
- Joint Council No. 42 Southern California Teamster, October 4, 1989 (Box 21, Folder 71)
- Joint Council No. 42 Southern California Teamster, Novmber 8, 1989 (Box 21, Folder 72)
- Joint Council No. 42 Southern California Teamster, December 13, 1989 (Box 21, Folder 73)
- Joint Council No. 42 Southern California Teamster, January 17, 1990 (Box 21, Folder 74)
- Joint Council No. 42 Southern California Teamster, March 14, 1990 (Box 21, Folder 75)
- Joint Council No. 42 Southern California Teamster, April 11, 1990 (Box 21, Folder 76)
- Joint Council No. 42 Southern California Teamster, May 23, 1990 (Box 21, Folder 77)
- Joint Council No. 42 Southern California Teamster, June 13, 1990 (Box 21, Folder 78)
- Joint Council No. 42 Southern California Teamster, July 11, 1990 (Box 21, Folder 79)
- Joint Council No. 42 Southern California Teamster, August 8, 1990 (Box 21, Folder 80)
- Joint Council No. 42 Southern California Teamster, November 11, 1987 (Box 21, Folder 81)
- Joint Council No. 42 Southern California Teamster, December 9, 1987 (Box 21, Folder 82)
- Joint Council No. 42 Southern California Teamster, January 20, 1988 (Box 21, Folder 83)
- Joint Council No. 42 Southern California Teamster, February 24, 1988 (Box 21, Folder 84)
- Joint Council No. 42 Southern California Teamster, March 23, 1988 (Box 21, Folder 85)
- Joint Council No. 42 Southern California Teamster, April 20, 1988 (Box 21, Folder 86)
- Rocky Mountain Teamster, June 2008 (Box 21, Folder 87)
- Joint Council No. 42 Southern California Teamster, May 18, 1988 (Box 21, Folder 88)
- Joint Council No. 42 Southern California Teamster, June 15, 1988 (Box 21, Folder 89)